Who are you?
Have you come from the real world?
That's right.
My name's Sinon.
Asuna sent me to save you and
Bercouli from Emperor Vecta.
I'm sorry I couldn't.
No.
Do not be.
His death is my fault.
Were the others safe when you left them?
They were heading for some ruins,
but the Red Knights from
my world are closing in.
They'll catch up to him soon.
In that case, I must co-join them.
No, Alice.
You can't.
You need to keep heading south,
to the World's End Altar.
If you touch the console—I
mean, the crystal panel,
the people on the real-world
side will bring you to them.
Why should I?
Emperor Vecta is dead, is he not?
Sort of.
But it's not that simple.
If someone from the real world
dies here, they only die here.
In my world, they're still alive.
Vecta was a shell with
a real worlder in it.
You can destroy the shell, but the person,
the one inside, can come
back here if they want.
So the villain uncle
sacrificed himself to kill.
He's not really dead.
He has simply vanished and will awaken in
your world alive, as if nothing happened.
Was it all for nothing?
All this death?
Are you saying Uncle died in vain?
What kind of duel is it, where
only one risks their life?
That is no duel!
That is nothing but a farce!
You know, Kirito,
you don't think his intentions in
suffering are for nothing, do you?
He's from the real world too,
and it's the same for him.
If he died here, he wouldn't really die.
But still, like, everything
he felt here was real.
His wounds, the pain he suffered, the
damage to his soul, they're all real.
He's my friend.
I love him.
I care about him.
The same goes for Asuna
and so many other people,
and we're all hoping and
praying he pulls through this.
Back home,
none of us knew why he put himself
through so much in a world he wasn't from.
He did it for you, Alice.
All he wanted was to save you, and
that's real, as real as your uncle.
He fought with everything he had,
suffered all those wounds, and in the
end, he gave his life to save you.
Sinon, if I leave through the World's
End Altar, what becomes of my family,
the people whom I love?
Will I be trapped there, or can I return?
You can, whenever.
her.
As long as you and the
Underworld are both safe.
Very well then.
I shall head south for the
altar.
Part of me still resists this course
of action, but they both wished it.
Uncle, as well
as Kirito.
You should go join the others though.
Hurry.
If that Vecta guy comes back,
I think he'll come back here.
If he does, I'll keep him
busy, buy you a little time.
I appreciate it, and I swear your
efforts shall not be in vain.
...
The color of your soul is what
is the color of your soul?
What's the most important thing to me?
Thank you.
Oh, my God.
If this is how I die,
at least the previous champ won't
laugh when I see him in the afterlife.
Why does my heart hurt so
I just want to cut him?
I want to savor that battle again
feel it burn down to my core
I want to sever those fists
which are harder than diamonds.
That was my only desire.
But this pain.
Slice and hack and slash away.
And at the end of your blood-smeared path,
you will find the key
to breaking your curse.
At least, you might.
Ah, I see.
For your service, I thank you.
Thank you for yours as well, Yoyobi.
You are tired.
Go. Rest now.
Your sword broke. I'm sorry.
It's all my fault.
No.
Do not trouble yourself.
At long last, I know why
I have this compulsion.
To find what I don't want to slash.
To find what I want to protect.
I was fighting toward one goal.
That goal was you.
Damn it.
I wish we could have
had a family together.
We could have had ourselves
the strongest kid ever.
way stronger than the previous champ.
Stronger than me.
The strongest pugilist of us all.
Hardly.
Our child would be a knight.
If we can keep the pressure on, this
will be wrapped up real soon, I hope.
You're the best.
I mean it.
I can't begin to thank you.
Oh, come on.
You don't have to thank anyone.
I owe you like nobody's business.
Heck you and kitty dude always
had my back it's the least
I could do by the way um he
here he's safe in a wagon just
down there after this is
over you should definitely go
talk to him maybe one of your
dumb jokes will wake him up?
Man, you're as harsh as ever.
It'll be okay.
I know it. Fast pants!
We'll pull through, I'm sure.
Damn straight!
Alrighty, let's switch back
in and finish this. Right.
You okay?
I just saw someone...
up there.
Haven't we seen that guy somewhere before?
Hmm?
He's too far away to tell.
And with his hood up, I can't...
see his... face.
Are you kidding?
There's no way!
Not here!
Am I seeing... ghosts now?
But that's crazy!
There's no such thing!
Well, look at him.
That black cloak?
No, it's a leather poncho.
That's the leader of Laughing Coffin.
It's Pooh.
In here?
Look, it's the players from Japan.
No more.
Please God, no more!
Holy crap, we're in for it now!
This match ain't from America.
Or Japan.
We're so screwed.
They're from China and Korea!
I don't want to enlist.
If the army allowed
atmospheres, I wouldn't mind.
Links start.
A bunch of Korean, American, and
Chinese gamers made a new VR game.
And their test server has just been
hacked by a group of Japanese players.
They're attacking the testers right now.
Someone's always spoiling
someone else's fun.
Bunch of jerks.
Those big dumb ones are the bad guys!
They must be the Japanese.
They look organized.
The big red ones must be the testers.
They're getting hammered.
Wait a sec.
The Japanese look like
they're fighting them off.
Hey, Amunfeiz.
Have you seen that video yet?
Yeah, Mei-Mei-Shang. Just now.
It's crazy, huh? I'll say.
Hurry up and download the
client and let's get in there.
What client?
Oh.
Seeking volunteers to help save the testers
from the vicious Japanese attackers?
For anyone who'd like to join,
please download the required
client software to your atmosphere.
I'm still not sold on the
Japanese attackers' part.
It's so weird.
Meixiang, what do you think?
This legit?
It I don't know yet
but if what they say is
true then our fellow gamers are in trouble
and could use all the help they can get
yeah I don't know about that it all sounds
fishy install the client and find out for
yourself I'm diving in now see if I see ya
I got nothing better to do it looks like a
bunch of my friends already dove in there.
It's him.
I know this guy, those
eyes, a face, I know him.
Son, I'm sorry.
Come in, Higa.
You doing okay?
Yeah, so far.
We should be there soon.
The bulkhead's maybe a couple
minutes down from us still.
Sounds good.
When you get to it, let me know.
I'll tell the guys with
Ichiemon to send him in. Roger.
Hey, Yuna.
Thanks again for going with him.
I owe you big time when
this is over. You got it.
Holy crap, that's a lot of nerds.
How many are in there total?
What the hell?
It's the alarm for the bulkhead!
Someone's gone and flipped the locks!
Don't just stand there
and check the corridor!
Damn it!
The highjackers know about Ichiemon!
You there yet?
We're almost to the maintenance connector.
Ten more meters to go.
All right.
I'll keep an eye on Kirito's luck flight
and let you know if anything happened.
Good luck, Higa. Oh, hell.
Hey, Moonphase!
Now time.
What took you so long?
Sorry, guys.
I was getting ready for class.
So, uh, what do we do now?
The terrain looks sick.
Are those guys the Japanese players?
Listen up, people!
I want to thank all of you for
diving in here and helping the cause.
Bad news is, we're too late to save the
Alpha Testers in this part of the map.
They were killed out by the
Japanese a little while ago.
But don't worry.
We got them logged back
in to another location,
and they're continuing
their work from there.
Since the Japanese hacked our server,
they got access to all the
high-spec gear they want.
They're also blocking us
devs from our admin access.
What that means is, we have
to fight using default gear!
Cowards!
Let's kick them all out!
Yeah!
Let's protect our server!
That's the spirit!
Patriots don't need fancy soldiers!
God, my head's ringing.
Mine too.
It's like my brains been taken over
hang on if he's really a devil he says
You could just cut the power to the server
Sit this one out, Asuna.
Let us have the glory
for once. He's right.
We've been itching for a challenge.
Sheyta!
Claps!
Here it is, the maintenance connector.
Matching in now.
Yes!
That was easier than I thought.
I got Kirito's and Asuna's STLs.
And the two girls in Roppongi, too.
We got this.
Don't move!
Oh, oh,
oh.
How long have you
created a
long time?
It's so sad that you don't
want to smile on your face.
Oh, oh,
oh,
oh.
Thank you.
Next time, Code 871.